https://www.detroitlions.com/about-us/privacy-policy/index

Skip to main content
Detroit Lions Privacy Policy | Detroit Lions - DetroitLions.com
Detroit Lions Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
August 26, 2020
The Detroit Lions' organization ("we," "our," "us") respects your privacy and values your trust and confidence. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to our websites, mobile applications, and other online and mobile services that link to or post this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Services"), and explains how we collect, use, disclose and secure information through the Services. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information.
By using the Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that is collected or obtained through sites or services that do not link to this Privacy Policy or information collected by the NFL or the other NFL member clubs (the "Member Clubs").
Organization of this Policy:
Information we Collect
Information You Provide
Information Which May Be Automatically Collected
Use and Sharing of Information Collected
Service Providers
Affiliated and NFL Entities
Select Business Partners
Third-Party Ad Serving
Information you Provide
You generally are not required to provide information about yourself when you visit the Services. However, we may ask you for some or all of the following types of information when you register with our Services, sign up for contests or sweepstakes, use a send-to-a-friend feature, participate in surveys, access various content or features, submit comments or content, or directly contact us with questions or feedback:
Contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, and telephone number;
Unique identifiers, such as a username or password;
Demographic information, such as gender;
Financial information, such as credit card or other payment information;
Communications preferences;
Search queries;
Comments and other information posted in our interactive online forums;
Correspondence and other information that you send to us; and
Additional information as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.
Information we May Automatically Collect or Log
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files when you use the Services, including:
Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area;
Other unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers;
Your browser type and operating system;
Sites you visited before and after visiting the Services;
Pages you view and links you click on within the Services;
Information collected through cookies, web beacons, local shared objects, and other technologies;
Information about your interactions with email messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were received, opened, or forwarded; and
Standard Server Log Information including request date/time, page requested, HTTP code, bytes served and referrer.
Usage Tracking Information
The Detroit Lions' organization and our partners, affiliates, and analytics or service providers use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts. These technologies are used for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or Services. The Detroit Lions' organization participates in the Adobe Marketing Cloud Device Co-op to better understand how you use our website and apps across the various devices you use, and to deliver tailored promotions. In addition, we may allow third parties to place and read their own cookies, web beacons, Local Shared Objects, and similar technologies to collect information through the Services. For example, our third party service providers may use these technologies to collect information that helps us with traffic measurement, research, and analytics.
Use of Information
We may use information that we collect through the Services for a variety of purposes, including:
To provide you with the products, promotions, services, newsletters, and information you request and respond to correspondence that we receive from you;
To contact you via email and otherwise about your account, products, services, contests, and events that we think might be of interest to you;
To send you promotional material or special offers on our behalf or on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties;
To maintain or administer the Services, perform business analyses, or for other internal purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Services, and other products and services we offer;
To publish stories, comments, photos, and other information posted in our interactive online features;
To send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running;
To customize and personalize your use of the Services; and
As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about content on our site, we will ask for your friend's name and email address in order to send your friend a one time email inviting him or her to visit the site. If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at privacypolicy@lions.nfl.net
Sharing of Information
We are committed to maintaining your trust, and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share the information we collect. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy.
Service Providers: We may share your information with service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf, such as to host the Services, fulfill orders, provide products and services, manage databases, perform analyses, process credit card payments, provide customer service, or send communications for us.
Subsidiaries and Affiliates: We may share your information with all members of the NFL Family, including, without limitation, NFL Properties LLC, NFL International LLC, NFL Enterprises LLC, NFL Ventures, L.P., and NFL Ventures, Inc.
Select Business Partners: With your permission, we may share your information with select business partners so that they can provide you with special offers, promotional materials, and other materials that may be of interest to you. For example, you may be presented with an opportunity to have certain information shared with our third party business partners when you enter a contest or sweepstakes or elect to receive marketing offers or other information. If you do not elect to have your information shared, it will not be shared with such third parties. We take measures to help ensure that our partners protect the confidentiality, integrity, and security of any information we share with them. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners, which may use your information for their own purposes.
Third Party Ad Serving: We may use third parties to serve advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users' online activities over time and across different websites. To manage your preferences, you may opt out here. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.
Business Transfer: If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, a business reorganization, or similar event, we may transfer your information as part of such transaction. You will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our website of any changes in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
Administrative or Legal Process: We may disclose your information to third parties in order to protect the legal rights, safety, and security of our organization, our corporate affiliates, subsidiaries, business partners, and the users of our Services; enforce our Terms of Use; respond to and resolve claims or complaints; prevent fraud or for risk management purposes; and comply with or respond to law enforcement or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government or other entity, whether or not legally required.
Interactive Features: We may share information with third parties when you post a message, information or photo to a user profile or a public area of the Services, such as a chat room, forum, blog, or other community tool. If you post to these interactive features, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure that parties who have access to such information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when using these features.
Contests or Sweepstakes: We periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through or promoted on the Website and/or Mobile App that will require registration or the submission of personal information. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes (see the rules of each contest or sweepstakes for details about how your personal information will be used, including postings to the Website). In some instances, a third party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Website, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we have no control over the information collected and accordingly urge you to review the advertiser's or sponsor's privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.
Other Parties With Your Express or Implied Consent: We may share information with third parties when you consent to such sharing. For example, if you win a contest or sweepstakes, we may ask your permission to publicly post certain information on the Services identifying you as the winner.
Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographic and usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations.
Other Websites, Applications and Services
Social Networking Services
Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the Share This button, or interactive mini programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. In some instances, such as within our mobile application and certain parts of our site, if you leave a comment within the community forum on our site, you must login to your Facebook account to do so. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party websites or services.
Co-Branding
The Detroit Lions may offer some services in connection with a third party via a co-branded webpage, such as for navigation, ride hailing services, purchasing/selling tickets, etc. Where you have provided personal information on a webpage that is co-branded with another company, then that personal information may made available to both the Detroit Lions and the co-branding partner. Whereas the Detroit Lions' data practices and your choice options are described in this Privacy Policy, we encourage you to consult the co-branding partner's privacy policy to ensure that you understand how it intends to use your information and how you may exercise control over it.
Links to Other Websites
The Services may contain links to other websites or online services that are operated and maintained by third parties and that are not under the control of or maintained by us. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by us of those other websites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. This Privacy Policy does not apply to this third party content. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party websites or services.
Mobile Applications
When you download and use our mobile app, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID"). Certain features within the app, such as playing a game, may require you to log into your Facebook account to use them. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Push Notifications.
We may send you push notifications from time to time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level.
Geo-Location Services
We collect your location-based information for the purpose of locating a place that you may be searching for in your area, navigations, or ride hailing services in connection with our third party partners. We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the sole purpose of providing you these services. We may share your geolocation data with third parties for the purpose of them serving you ads for places (such as restaurants) in your area, for navigation, or for ride hailing services. If you do not wish to allow us to share your information in this manner or if you would like to opt-out of location based services please contact us at privacypolicy@lions.nfl.net. You may also opt-out of location based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level. We may also work in conjunction with third party partners who may use technologies such as geofencing and beacons to identify fans attending a game, and contact fans via an in-app feature in order to provide a better stadium experience. To opt-out of geofencing, you may disable the app's location permissions on your device.
Usage Data
We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile applications on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile application.
We may partner with a Third Party to provide a fan-participatory lightshow. That Third Party will offer a wireless content application through a Third Party Sales Location. If you choose to participate in that event you will be subject to the additional terms of use agreements related to that Third Party Sales Location and we expressly disclaim any responsibility or liability for any damage, loss or injury arising out of or provided through that Third Party Sales Location. If you chose to download that wireless content application, you should be aware that it uses the microphone on your mobile phone to sync the device to the lightshow music. The audio analysis used by the application relies on frequencies higher than those used to listen to the human voice, and in any event, no data used in connection with the synchronization using your mobile phone at the beginning of that event will ever be recorded or sent to any server.
Access, Choice and Retention
Upon request the Detroit Lions organization will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your information changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Services, you may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by signing into your account and making the required changes, by emailing our Customer Support at privacypolicy@lions.nfl.net, or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
You may choose to receive promotional emails, newsletters, and similar communications from us. You may opt out of receiving commercial emails from us by clicking on the opt-out or "unsubscribe" link included in the commercial emails you receive. Please note that opt-out requests may take up to 10 days to be effective. Your opt-out request will not apply to messages that you request or that are not commercial in nature. For example, we may contact you concerning any purchases you have made with us, even if you opt out of receiving unsolicited commercial email messages.
Security
We have adopted security procedures to help protect against loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to the information you provide to us. For example, if we collect financial information, we will use encryption software to help protect this information when it is in transit. Please note, however, that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to the Services and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your information.
Children's Privacy
The Services do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13. If we are made aware we have collected personal information from a child under 13 years old in a manner that is inconsistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"), we will delete this information as soon as possible.
The website is a general audience website. However, we do collect information about children under 13 from parents so they may sign their child up for our Cub Club. The information we collect is your child's name, gender, date of birth and the address provided by a parent, guardian or purchaser of the Detroit Lions Cub Club membership. We use this information to allow you to sign your child up for the Cub Club and for you to receive Detroit Lions merchandise as a part of the Cub Club membership, for your child. If you no longer wish to allow your child to be part of the Cub Club or wish to delete all information collected about your child, please contact us at privacypolicy@lions.nfl.net
We will not share your child's personal information with any third party for any reason. If you feel we have collected personal information from your child directly, please contact us at privacypolicy@lions.nfl.net to request immediate deletion of that information.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Services after any modification to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the new terms. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Services prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
California Residents
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides residents of California with various rights related to their personal information. These include the right to information about the types of personal information we collect, access to copies of that information and, subject to certain limitations, the right to demand that your personal information be erased. The policies we have instituted to comply with the CCPA may be found at https://www.detroitlions.com/about-us/privacy-policy/CA
Although by its terms the CCPA applies only to residents of California, in the interests of fairness and transparency, we afford these rights to all users of our Services and will honor requests for disclosure or deletion of your personal information under our CCPA policy whether or not you are a resident of California.
Do-Not Track
In some cases, third parties may be able to collect information about a user's online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our Services. Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to the websites with which the user communicates. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, we currently do not take action in response to these signals. If and when a final standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals.
International Users
Please note that the Services are directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States. While some of these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection as your own, we commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this Policy.
Third-Party Ad Serving and Audience and Traffic Measurement Services
We may use third-parties to serve advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users' online activities over time and across different websites. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by participating companies in the following consumer choice mechanisms, please visit: Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)'s self-regulatory opt-out page (http://optout.aboutads.info/) and mobile application-based "AppChoices" download page (https://youradchoices.com/appchoices). In the mobile environment, most mobile operating systems offer device-based opt-out choices that are transmitted to companies providing interest-based advertising. To set an opt-out preference for a mobile device identifier (such as Apple's IDFA or Android's GAID), visit the device manufacturer's current choice instructions pages, or read more about sending signals to limit ad tracking for your operating system here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices. The Services may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow users to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. Nielsen believes that you should have a choice about whether to contribute to our research and insights. To opt out of Nielsen measurement, you need only to activate the "Limit Ad Tracking" (for iOS devices) or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" (for Android devices) option in your devices settings. For web, please visit: http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy to learn more about the Nielsen digital measurement products and your choices in regard to them.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact privacypolicy@lions.nfl.net, or by mail at
222 Republic Drive
Allen Park, Michigan 48101
Attn: Website Privacy Policy & General Counsel
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
Big left arrow icon
Big right arrow icon
Close icon
Copy Url
Three dots icon
Down arrow icon
Email icon
Email icon
InstagramTwitterFacebookSnapchatShop IconProfile Overlay
AvatarAddAirplayArrow LeftArrow RightArrow UpArrow DownAudioBack 5sBack 10sBack 30sCalendarChartCheckDownLeftRightUpChromecast OffChromecast OnCloseClosed CaptionsBench OffBench OnBroad OffBroad OnVertical OffVertical OnCommentDockDoneDownloadDraftFantasyFilterForward 5sForward 10sForward 30sFull Screen OffFull Screen OnGamepassGamesInsightsKeyLeaveLiveCombineDraftFantasyMenu GamesMenu NetworkMenu NewsMenu PlayoffsMenu Pro BowlMenu ShopMenu StandingsMenu StatsMenu Super BowlMenu TeamsMenu TicketsMenuMore HorizontalMore VerticalMy LocationNetworkNewsPauseplayMultiple PlayersSingle PlayerPlaylistPlayoffsPro BowlPurgeRefreshRemoveReplaySearchSettingsShare AndroidShare Copy URLShare EmailShare FacebookShare InstagramShare iOSShare SnapchatShare TwitterSkip NextSkip PreviousStandingsStarStatsSwapTeamsTicketsVideoVisibility OffVisibility OnVolume HiVolume LowVolume MediumVolume MuteWarningWebsite
Caret downCaret upAt
The browser you are using is no longer supported on this site. It is highly recommended that you use the latest versions of a supported browser in order to receive an optimal viewing experience. The following browsers are supported: Chrome, Edge (v80 and later), Firefox and Safari.
Got it!
